Finding aid for the Paulist Productions records LSC.2300
UCLA Library Special Collections
Paulist Productions records
ca. 1937-2000
1960-1987
UCLA Library Special Collections
Paulist Productions
LSC.2300
36 linear feet (82 boxes, 3 flat boxes, 2 shoe boxes)
Paulist Productions was founded in Los Angeles in 1960 by Ellwood "Bud" Kieser (b. March 27, 1929-d. September 16, 2000), a Catholic priest and member of the Paulist Fathers. Its initial television series, Insight, originally consisted of little more than Father Kieser delivering a lecture about Christian values on an empty stage. Though production values remained modest, the syndicated program's non-dogmatic, ecumenical approach was soon able to attract top-flight Hollywood talent who would often donate their fees back to the company. In its quarter-century of activity, Insight addressed issues such as poverty, racism, and war from a liberal perspective, while still maintaining a resolutely anti-communist stance, and winning nine Daytime Emmy Awards. In addition to Insight, Paulist Productions was responsible for the feature film Romero, and for a number of television movies and specials. It also produced several short films for classroom use. The collection consists mostly of scripts, photographs, and publicity material for Insight, as well as for various other productions. Many scripts are annotated, and appear in multiple drafts. Photographs tend to consist of scene stills and off-camera photographs, in the form of prints, negatives, contact sheets, and color transparencies. Publicity material consists primarily of press releases. There is a small amount of information about distribution, but virtually no production records or correspondence apart from cast and staff lists and notes written in scripts. There is also a significant amount of material about Ellwood Kieser. Most of this material consists of photographs documenting his travels and on-set activities. There are also many examples of Father Kieser's writing, though his autobiography, Hollywood Priest, is not present in draft or published form.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Donated by Joseph Kim on behalf of Paulist Productions, May 5, 2015.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9978157993606533
Biography/History
Paulist Productions was founded in Los Angeles in 1960 by Ellwood "Bud" Kieser (b. March 27, 1929-d. September 16, 2000), a Catholic priest and member of the Paulist Fathers. Its initial television series, Insight, originally consisted of little more than Father Kieser delivering a lecture about Christian values on an empty stage. Though production values remained modest, the syndicated program's non-dogmatic, ecumenical approach was soon able to attract top-flight Hollywood talent who would often donate their fees back to the company. Actors such as Martin Sheen, Edward Asner, and Patty Duke starred in several episodes each, and dozens of other luminaries (for example, Irene Dunne, Carol Burnett, Walter Matthau, and Louis Gossett, Jr.) appeared in just one or two shows. Rod Serling, Michael Crichton, and William Peter Blatty were among the writers who offered scripts for the program, and Arthur Hiller and Ted Post directed several episodes each. In its quarter-century of activity, Insight addressed issues such as poverty, racism, and war from a liberal perspective, while still maintaining a resolutely anti-communist stance, and winning nine Daytime Emmy Awards.
In addition to Insight, Paulist Productions was responsible for the feature film Romero, and for a number of television movies and specials. It also produced several short films for classroom use.
In 1974 Father Kieser established the Humanitas Prize, which honors film and television writing that reflects on the human condition and inspires compassion in viewers.
Though no longer producing an ongoing television series, Paulist Productions remains an active company.
Scope and Content
The collection consists mostly of scripts, photographs, and publicity material for the syndicated television program Insight, as well as for various other productions. Many scripts are annotated, and appear in multiple drafts. Photographs tend to consist of scene stills and off-camera photographs, in the form of prints, negatives, contact sheets, and color transparencies. Publicity material consists primarily of press releases. There is a small amount of information about distribution, but virtually no production records or correspondence apart from cast and staff lists and notes written in scripts.
There is also a significant amount of material about Paulist Productions founder Ellwood Kieser. Most of this material consists of photographs documenting his travels and on-set activities. There are also many examples of Father Kieser's writing, though his autobiography, Hollywood Priest, is not present in draft or published form.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series, most of which correspond to a production banner:
Series 1. Insight
Series 2. Capital Cities specials
Series 3. Reflections
Series 4. Bloomin' Human Films
Series 5. Values: Educating for Responsibility
Series 6. Buchanan High
Series 7. Miscellaneous productions
Series 8. Unrealized productions
Series 9. Father Ellwood "Bud" Kieser
Motion pictures -- Religious aspects -- Catholic Church; Motion pictures in education; Motion pictures in church work; Christian television programs; Paulist Productions -- Archives; Kieser, Ellwood E.
- Series 1. Insight, 1960-1984
  Scope and Content
  This series contains material on the syndicated television series that ran from 1960-1984. Photographs generally consist of black and white prints, negatives, and contact sheets. Color transparencies are not uncommon. More unusual are color prints and negatives.
  Organization and Arrangement
  This arrangement reflects the original arrangement of the donor. Individual episodes are first listed in alphabetical order. The first subseries consists of scripts that had been in springback and three-ring binders in numerical order. The second subseries consists of clippings that had been arranged chronologically in three-ring binders. The third subseries consists of files that concern Insight generally, rather than specific episodes.
  - The Agitator [#138], 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Script [no writer credited]; photographs [including off-camera shots of Ruth Hussey and Brian Keith].
  - All Out [#388], 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Three scripts by John Zodrow [one heavily annotated]; reviews.
  - All Out [#388] - photographs, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - All the Little Plumes in Pain [#193], undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Script by Donald Munson; photographs.
  - All the Things I've Never Liked [#205], 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Script by James E. Miller [lightly annotated]; photographs.
  - The Alleluia Kid [#406], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Script by Richard Fielder; photographs.
  - And the Walls Came Tumblin' Down [#369], 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one heavily annotated].
  - And the Walls Came Tumblin' Down [#369]- photographs, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes off-camera shots of Jack Albertson and Martin Sheen.
  - And Who Has Ever Seen Xanadu? [#180], undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Script by James Moser; photographs.
  - Arnstein's Miracle [#410], 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Script by Lan O'Kun; publicity material; photographs.
  - Attention Must Be Paid [#360], 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Three scripts by Lan O'Kun [one heavily annotated]; cast and staff list.
  - Attention Must Be Paid [#360] - photographs, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Ballad of Alma Gerlayne [#202], 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Ed Waters [one annotated]; photographs.
  - Beelzebub and the Bolsheviks [#103], 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Script [no writer credited]; photographs [including off-camera shots of Irene Dunne].
  - Belfast -- Black on Green [#412], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by William P. McGivern [one annotated]; reviews; cast and staff list.
  - Belfast -- Black on Green [#412] - photographs, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Bird on the Mast [#341], 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Script [by John Meredyth Lucas]; photographs.
  - Blind Man's Bluff [#395], 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Script by Lan O'Kun; photographs.
  - Blood Strike [#361], 1973 and 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by David Moessinger [one annotated]; photographs.
  - Boss Toad [#148], 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Script by Dehl Franke; photographs.
  - Bourbon in Suburbia [#322], 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by John Meredyth Lucas [one heavily annotated]; cast and staff list; discussion notes; photographs.
  - A Box for Mr. Lipton [#342], 1972 and 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one heavily annotated]; cast and staff list; study guides.
  - A Box for Mr. Lipton [#342] - photographs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Boy and the Bomb [#137], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Script [annotated; no writer credited]; photographs [including off-camera shots of Jeanne Crain and John Forsythe].
  - The Breakthrough [#133], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Script [heavily annotated; no writer credited]; photographs [including off-camera shots of Bettye Ackerman and Edmond O'Brien].
  - Brothers in the Dark [#152], undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Script by E. Sarsfield Waters [lightly annotated]; photographs.
  - Butterfly [#456], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Pamela Douglas [one lightly annotated]; publicity material.
  - Butterfly [#456] - photographs, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Capitalist [#141], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Script by William J. Donnelly; photographs.
  - Cargoes [#423], 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by William P. McGivern;cast and crew lists; publicity material.
  - Cargoes [#423] - photographs, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Celebration in Fresh Powder [#366], undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Ed Waters [one heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - Charlie You Made the Night Too Long [#215], 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Script by William P. McGivern [heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - Checkmate [#421], 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Three scripts by Lan O'Kun; publicity material.
  - Checkmate [#421] - photographs, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chipper [#380], 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one heavily annotated]; study guides.
  - Chipper [#380] - photographs, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Christ, Caesar and Conscience [#104], 1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Script [no writer credited]; photographs.
  - Christmas 2025 [#408], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Three scripts by John McGreevey [one heavily annotated]; publicity material.
  - Christmas 2025 [#408] - photographs, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clearing House [#453], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Ben Elisco; publicity material.
  - Clearing House [#453] - photographs, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Clown of Freedom [#374], 1974 and 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Treatment; three scripts by Terrance Sweeney, S.J. [one heavily annotated]; cast and staff lists; publicity material.
  - The Clown of Freedom [#374] - photographs, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    Includes off-camera shots of Martin Sheen and others.
  - The Coffee House [#174], undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Script by Walter Bedlander & Barry Oringer; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Efrem Zimbalist, Jr].
  - The Coming of the Clone [#363], 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Three scripts by John T. Dugan [two annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - Confrontation [#328], 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Script by John T. Dugan; photographs.
  - Consider the Zebra [#318], 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by John T. Dugan [one lightly annotated]; photographs.
  - The Conspirator [#134], 1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Script [no writer credited]; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Vera Miles and Dan O'Herlihy].
  - The Crime of Innocence [#368], 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Three scripts by David Moessinger [one heavily annotated].
  - The Crime of Innocence [#368] - photographs, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Cross in the Crisis [#124], 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Two annotated scripts [no writer credited]; photographs.
  - The Cross of Russia [#151], 1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Crunch on Spruce Street [#332], 1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Three scripts by William P. McGivern [two annotated].
  - Crunch on Spruce Street [#332] - photographs, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cry of Terror [#323], 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Script by Richard Alan Simmons; photographs.
  - Cum Laude, Come Lonely [#399], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by Lydia A. Wiggins; photographs.
  - The Dangerous Airs of Amy Clark [#321], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Script by William P. McGivern [annotated]; photographs.
  - The Day Everything Went Wrong [#452], 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by Ellwood E. Kieser, C.S.P.; publicity material.
  - The Day Everything Went Wrong [#452] - photographs, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Day God Died [#312], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Three scripts by James E. Moser [two annotated]; study guides.
  - The Day God Died [#312] - photographs, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Death of Simon Jackson [#214], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Robert L. Goodwin [one annotated]; photographs.
  - The Death of Superman [#331], 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Four scripts by John Zodrow [two annotated]; study guides.
  - The Death of Superman [#331] - photographs, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Death of the Elephant [#345], undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Script by Jack Hanrahan; photographs.
  - A Decision to Love [#441], 1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by Richard Fielder; publicity material; photographs.
  - Diary of a Beatnik [#143], 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Divine Jew [#2], 1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Two scripts [one heavily annotated; no writer credited].
  - The Dog That Bit You [#155], 1965 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Script by John T. Kelley [annotated]; photographs.
  - The Domino Effect [#437], 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Script by William McGivern [annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - Don't Let Me Catch You Praying [#176], undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Script by Richard Breen; photographs.
  - Don't Elbow Me Off the Earth [#168], 1966 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by Theodore Apstein; photographs.
  - A Dry Commitment [#189], 1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Script by Donald Munson [annotated]; photographs.
  - Dutton's Choice [#451], 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Josef Anderson; publicity material.
  - Dutton's Choice [#451] - photographs, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Ecce Homo [#113/126], 1962 and 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Two scripts [no writer credited]; study guides.
  - Eddie [#367], 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Jim McGinn [one heavily annotated]; cast and staff lists.
  - Eddie [#367] - photographs, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Edith Stein Story [#128] - photographs, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Every Ninety Seconds [#446], 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Script by Jim McGinn; publicity material; photographs.
  - Exit [#326], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Script by John W. Zodrow [annotated]; study guides; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Eye of the Camel [#364], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by William McGivern [annotated]; photographs.
  - Fabric of Freedom [#108/120], 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Face of Tyranny [#101], 1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Two scripts [no writer credited].
  - Faith, a Reason to Live, a Reason To Die [#112/#125], 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Script [one heavily annotated; no writer credited]; photographs.
  - Fat Hands and a Diamond Ring [#192], 1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Script by John D.F. Black; photographs.
  - The Fiddler [#443], 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Ellwood Kieser, C.S.P.; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Fire Within [#161], 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Script by E. Sarsfield Waters [heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - Fisher of Men [#153], 1963-1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Copy of a letter from Ellwood Kieser to the New York office of the Paulist Fathers; script [no writer identified]; photographs; motion picture film frames.
  - Five Without Faces [#338], undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Tom Caramagno [one annotated].
  - Five Without Faces [#338] - photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Flawed Magi [#416], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by Leon Tokatyan from a story by Diana Kay Bell Tokatyan [one heavily annotated]; study guide.
  - The Flawed Magi [#416] - photographs, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - For Better or Worse [#136], 1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - For Love or Money [#449], 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Publicity material; reviews; photographs.
  - For the Love of Annie [#400], 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun; photographs [includes off-camera shots of John Astin and Patty Duke].
  - The Freak [#343], 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by John W. Zodrow [one annotated].
  - The Freak [#343] - photographs, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Friends [#351], undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Script by Lan O'Kun [annotated]; photographs.
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way [#182], 1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Script by Carol Sobieski; photographs.
  - The Game Room [#455], 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by Leon Tokatyan and Diane Bell Tokatyan; publicity material.
  - The Game Room [#455] - photographs, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Ghetto Trap [#203], 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Two scripts by Maureen Daly; photographs.
  - Girl in Free Fall [#397], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Script by Lydia Wiggins; photographs.
  - God and the Atheists [#114] - photographs, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - God in the Dock [#428], 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Three scripts by Ellwood Kieser, C.S.P. [one annotated]; cast and staff lists; study guides; publicity material.
  - God in the Dock [#428] - photographs, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - God's Guerillas [#438], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by John McGreevey; publicity material; photographs.
  - Goodbye [#430], undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The Governor's Mansion [#173], undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Script by Harry Julian Fink; photographs.
  - Graduation Day [#354], 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Three scripts by Jim McGinn [one annotated]; study guides; photographs.
  - The Greatest Madness of Them All: I Am [#325], 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Script by Thomas C. Caramagno [annotated]; photographs.
  - A Gun for Mandy [#447], 1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Incomplete script [no writer credited]; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Hang-Up [#186] (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Script by E. Sarsfield Waters; stills.
  - Happy Birthday Marvin [#358], 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one annotated]; study guides.
  - Happy Birthday Marvin [#358] - photographs, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Includes off-camera shots of Anne Francis and Bob Newhart.
  - The Hate Syndrome [#172}, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Script by Rod Serling [annotated]; photographs.
  - He Lived with Us, He Ate with Us, What Else, Dear? [#195], 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by William P. McGivern; study guides; photographs.
  - The Heart of Liberty [#105], 1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Hell Hound Blues [#390], 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Script by J.S. Sugarhill; study guides; photographs.
  - The Hermit [#140], 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Script by Richard Breen; study guides; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Jane Wyman and Eftrem Zimbalist, Jr.].
  - Hey Hey Billy Raye [#329], 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Script by Ed Waters [annotated]; photographs.
  - Hey, Janitor [#365], 1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Two scripts by Jim Moser [one heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - Highest Bidder [#340], 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Script by Leon Tokatyan; study guides; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Jack Albertson, Howard Duff, and Ida Lupino].
  - His Feet Don't Stink [#394], 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Script by John Zodrow; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Hit Man [#454], 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by David Field; publicity material.
  - The Hit Man [#454] - photographs, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Includes off-camera shots of Patty Duke.
  - Holy Moses [#422], 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Four scripts by Lan O'Kun [two annotated]; publicity material.
  - Holy Moses [#422] - photographs, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Hunger Knows My Name [#384], 1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Two scripts by William P. McGivern [one annotated]; photographs.
  - I, Walowtah... [#375], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Script by David Zodrow; photographs.
    Other Finding Aids
    This episode was not distributed.
  - I Want to Die [#404], 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by Terrance Sweeney; publicity material; photographs.
  - I'm Gonna Be Free [#353], 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Script by Harvey Lerner and David Moessinger [annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - Incident on Danker Street [#320], 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Script by David Moessinger; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Incredible Man [#382], 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Lan O'Kun [one annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Invincible Weapon [#149] - photographs, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - I.O.U. My Brother [#123], 1962 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Is Anyone Listening? [#414], 1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Two scripts by John McGreevey [one annotated]; study guide; publicity material; photographs.
  - Is the 11:59 Late This Year? [#317], 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Script by Leon Tokatyan [annotated]; publicity material; study guides; photographs.
  - It's a Right-Handed World [#164] (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Script by Michael Gleason [heavily annotated]; photographs.
  - Jesus B.C. [#402], 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Three scripts by John T. Dugan [two annotated]; publicity material.
  - Jesus B.C. [#402] - photographs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - The Jesus Song [#355], 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Two scripts by Jack Hanrahan [one annotated]; study guides; publicity material; photographs.
  - Just Before Eve [#415], 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Publicity material; photographs [includes off-camera shots of Martin Sheen and Flip Wilson].
  - Juvie [#396] - photographs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - The Kid Show [#150] - photographs, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - The Killer [#132], 1962 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Killer [#349], 1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Script by Michael Crichton; photographs.
  - The King of the Penny Arcade [#377], 1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Two scripts by Michael Alan Humm; cast and staff lists.
  - The King of the Penny Arcade [#377] - photographs, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Last of the Great Male Chauvinists [#385], 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Publicity material; photographs.
  - The Late Great God [#206], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Two scripts by Ed Waters [one annotated]; study guides; publicity material; photographs.
  - The Least of My Brothers [#169], undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Script by John Meredyth Lucas [annotated]; cast and staff lists; study guides; publicity material; photographs.
  - Leave Me Alone, God [#450], 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Two scripts by John Sacret Young; publicity material; photographs.
  - Leroy [#409], 1977 and 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Two scripts by John Zodrow [one heavily annotated]; publicity material; photographs.
  - Little Miseries [#440], 1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Two scripts by Ben Elisco; publicity material; photographs.